grubmarket.com 2015-09-05

# GrubMarket - Privacy Policy

The GrubMarket Team wants you to be very comfortable  using our Services, including trusting us with securing your information.  As such we've developed this Privacy Policy that describes  how we collect, use, disclose, transfer, and store your information.  This Privacy Policy, incorporated by reference into the Terms of Use, governs your use of the Services.  Please review this Privacy Policy carefully. Your use of any of the Services indicates that you have read, accepted and agreed to GrubMarket's privacy practices, as outlined in this Privacy Policy, and any other applicable terms.

As used herein, the term "personal information" means information that can be associated with a specific person and could be used to identify that person.  We do not consider personal information to include information that has been made anonymous or aggregated so that it can no longer be used, whether in combination with other information or otherwise, to identify a specific person.

We may update this Privacy Policy at any time by posting the updated version on this site.  It is your responsibility to review this Privacy Policy periodically for changes.  Your continued use of any of the Services following the posting of the updated version will mean that you accept and agree to the updated Privacy Policy.

Information Collected or Received

We require a user to provide a valid email address and choose a username connected with using the Services.  Depending on which part of the Services you use, additional information may be collected, such as billing or payment information, telephone number, physical address, transactional information based on your use of the Services, correspondence sent through our Services, device ID, device type, geo-location information, computer and connection information, statistics on page views, traffic to and from the Site, referral URL, ad data, IP address and standard web log information.

You may optionally choose to provide your full name and other personal information (such as birthday, gender, location) to be publicly displayed.

You may connect to GrubMarket with an external application, in which case GrubMarket may receive some information from that other service.

We use cookies and other technologies to keep track of your online interaction with the Services and help understand how users interact with our Services, in order to provide a better overall experience.  If you want to disable cookies, you can do so by modifying your browser settings.  Check with your browser provider to find out how to disable cookies.  Please note that certain features of the Services will not be available once cookies are disabled.

Information Sharing and Registration with Social Media Websites

We offer sign-on services that allow you to use third party login credentials to access the Services.  You may also use the Services to share information with third party social media websites such as Facebook, Google Plus, Twitter, and others.

You may choose to provide us with access to certain personal information stored by such third party websites.  The personal information we have access to varies by website and is controlled by your privacy settings on that website and your consent.  By associating an account managed by a third party with your GrubMarket account and authorizing GrubMarket to have access to this information, you agree that GrubMarket may collect, use and store information from these websites in accordance with this Privacy Policy.

Use of Personal Information

We use personal information to: (1) provide and improve the Services; (2) personalize the website or other part of the Services for you, communicate with you, and offer you special GrubMarket promotions (such as Daily Deals Email); and (3) help enforce the Terms of Use, prevent fraud, and keep our Services safe.

Security

We take great care in securing your personal information, meaning preventing unauthorized access to any of it. The best tool we provide is the ability for you protect your account with a password. Choose one carefully, never share it with anyone you do not fully trust, and never store it on a device or computer accessible to the public or to people you do not fully trust.

GrubMarket encrypts your data while receiving or sending it to your device or computer. We use one of the strongest grade of encryptions to make it nearly impossible for anyone to intercept the information.

Data Retention

We keep your information as long as your account is active. For inactive accounts we keep the minimal information for the purposes of resolving disputes and satisfying legal obligations. 

Disclosure to Third Parties

At times GrubMarket may make certain personal information available to third parties that work with GrubMarket to provide the Services, or that help GrubMarket market to customers.  Personal information will only be shared by GrubMarket to provide or improve the Services; it will not be shared with third parties for their own independent marketing purposes without your consent.  We may combine your information with information we collect from other companies and use it to improve and personalize our Services, content and advertising.

GrubMarket may disclose your personal information if required to do so by law or in the good faith belief that such action is necessary: 

(1) to comply with any law, legal process, and/or requests from government authorities; (2) to protect and defend the rights or property of GrubMarket; (3) to enforce the Terms of Use; (4) to act in urgent circumstances to protect the personal safety of users of GrubMarket, the operation of the Services or the general public; or (5) for purposes of national security, law enforcement, or other issues of public importance, where disclosure is necessary or appropriate.

Additionally, in the event of a reorganization, merger, or sale we may transfer any and all personal information we have collected from our users to the relevant third party.

Communication Preferences

You can access, review, and change your personal information from the My Account page.  If you do not want to receive any marketing or promotional email or other communications from GrubMarket, you can either choose the opt-out option where it is available or contract GrubMarket customer support at [support@grubmarket.com](mailto:support@grubmarket.com).

Children

GrubMarket does not provide the Services to children.  If you are under 18, you may use GrubMarket.com only with the involvement of a parent or legal guardian.

Third Party Sites and Services

This Privacy Policy applies only to information we collect about you as a user of the Services.  It does not apply to information about you collected by a third party via its site or services linked to or otherwise accessible from using the Services.  The information collected or obtained by these third parties is subject to their own privacy policies.  Additionally, in the event you access part of the Services that is co-branded with a third party, such third party's privacy policy, in addition to this Privacy Policy, may also apply.

International Users

The Services are controlled, operated and administered by GrubMarket from our offices within the USA.  If you access the Services from a location outside the USA, you are solely responsible for compliance with all applicable local and international laws and regulations, including without limitation, those applicable to the international sale, purchase, and shipment of items.  By using the Services and providing your personal information to GrubMarket, you also consent to the collection, transfer, storage and processing of your personal information outside of your jurisdiction of residence.

Your California Privacy Rights

California Civil Code Section 1798.83, also known as the "Shine The Light" law, permits our customers who are California residents to request and obtain from us once a year, free of charge, information about the personal information (if any) we disclosed to third parties for direct marketing purposes in the preceding calendar year.  If applicable, this information would include a list of the categories of personal information that was shared and the names and addresses of all third parties with which we shared information in the immediately preceding calendar year.  If you are a California resident and would like to make such a request, please submit your request to [privacy@grubmarket.com](mailto:privacy@grubmarket.com).

Contact Us

If you have questions or concerns about this Privacy Policy, please contact us at [privacy@grubmarket.com](mailto:privacy@grubmarket.com).
